javascriptobfuscator.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy of Javascript Obfuscator

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

#### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

#### Do you keep my JavaScript source code?

No. The source code obfuscation is processed in server memory. You don't need to upload any Javascript files to the server. 

#### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

#### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

  By e-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9af3f4fcf5daf0fbecfbe9f9e8f3eaeef5f8fcefe9f9fbeef5e8b4f9f5f7)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
